<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My City App</string>
    <string name="category_fragment_label">Categories</string>
    <string name="recommended_fragment_label">Recommended</string>
    <!--Category -->
    <string name="coffee_shops">Coffee Shops</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="dog_friendly">Dog Friendly Restaurants</string>
    <string name="dog_parks">Dog Parks</string>
    <string name="shopping_center">Shopping Center</string>
    <!--Coffee Shops -->
    <string name="mad_lab_coffee">Mad Lab Coffee</string>
    <string name="mad_lab_coffee_subtitle">Mad Lab Coffee was launched out of a basement in downtown LA</string>
    <string name="mad_lab_coffee_details">Mad Lab Coffee was launched out of a basement in downtown LA by creators Andrew Sinclair and Sarah Sinclair with a focus on quality and the neighborhood of Los Angeles. Mad Lab has become one of the most recognizable roasters in Los Angeles and the International coffee community focusing on quality, seasonal, and relational driven coffees. The focus for all of Mad Lab’s coffees is the pursuit of sweetness and fruitiness.</string>
    <string name="mad_lab_coffee_hours">Open from 7am-6pm</string>
    <string name="mad_lab_coffee_location">6515 W Sunset Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90028</string>

    <string name="laidrey_coffee">Laidrey Coffee</string>
    <string name="laidre_coffee_subtitle">Stop by our cafe in Tarzana to sample our range of coffees alongside a menu of baked treats</string>
    <string name="laidre_coffee_details">Stop by our cafe in Tarzana to sample our range of coffees alongside a menu of baked treats, seasonal toasts, and more. We regularly host events throughout the month on our shop where we partner with local vendors, in addition to providing coffee bags, merchandise, and more for purchase in our cafe. We look forward to seeing you at Laidrey!</string>
    <string name="laidre_coffee_hours">Open M-Sun 7am - 5pm</string>
    <string name="laidre_coffee_location">18600 Venture Blvd., Tarzana, CA 91356</string>

    <string name="ten_speed_coffee">10 Speed Coffee</string>
    <string name="ten_speed_coffee_subtitle">Appealing to bicycle culture, this Calabasas and Santa Monica cafe does well-crafted espresso</string>
    <string name="ten_speed_coffee_details">Appealing to bicycle culture, this Calabasas and Santa Monica cafe does well-crafted espresso drinks and a light menu of teas and tonics to help cyclists to continue their routes. When in Santa Monica, the shop is a bright oasis to work or host in-person meetings or for a quick cup.</string>
    <string name="ten_speed_coffee_hours">Open from 6am - 4pm</string>
    <string name="ten_speed_coffee_location">1919 Santa Monica Blvd.,Santa Monica, CA 90404</string>

    <string name="the_boy_and_the_bear">The Boy and the Bear</string>
    <string name="the_boy_and_the_bear_subtitle">The Boy and the Bear is steadily moving on an expansion path with locations in Redondo Beach</string>
    <string name="the_boy_and_the_bear_details">The Boy and the Bear is steadily moving on an expansion path with locations in Redondo Beach, Westchester, Pasadena, Culver City, and a new cafe in Sherman Oaks. The warehouse-style interiors take on a cool, spacious, and serene vibe with plenty of well-crafted espresso drinks.</string>
    <string name="the_boy_and_the_bear_hours">Open from 7am - 4pm</string>
    <string name="the_boy_and_the_bear_location">350 N Pacific Coast Hwy, Redondo Beach, CA 90277</string>

    <string name="maru_coffee">Maru Coffee</string>
    <string name="maru_coffee_subtitle">An exercise in Korean minimalist design, Maru’s Los Feliz and the Arts District are incredibly pleasant places</string>
    <string name="maru_coffee_details">An exercise in Korean minimalist design, Maru’s Los Feliz and the Arts District are incredibly pleasant places to enjoy coffee in Los Angeles. The beans are roasted at its larger Arts District space and the Beverly Hills is a recent addition to secure a cup in the city.</string>
    <string name="maru_coffee_hours">Open from 8am - 5pm</string>
    <string name="maru_coffee_location">1936 Hillhurst Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90027</string>

    <!--Restaurants -->
    <string name="restaurant_orochon_ramen">Orochon Ramen</string>
    <string name="restaurant_orochon_ramen_subtitle">Small Japanese restaurant with a Wall of Fame for diners who can conquer the spiciest ramen bowl.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_orochon_ramen_details">Small Japanese restaurant with a Wall of Fame for diners who can conquer the spiciest ramen bowl.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_orochon_ramen_hours">Open Sun-Thur 11:30am - 10:30pm Friday and Saturday 11:30am - 11:00pm</string>
    <string name="restaurant_orochon_ramen_location">123 Astronaut E S Onizuka St, Los Angeles, California 90012</string>

    <string name="restaurant_slurpin_ramen_bar">Slurpin Ramen Bar</string>
    <string name="restaurant_slurpin_ramen_bar_subtitle">Staying traditional with style! Started in the heart of Koreatown</string>
    <string name="restaurant_slurpin_ramen_bar_details">Staying traditional with style! Started in the heart of Koreatown, Los Angeles 8th Street, slurpin ramen was created from ambition to bringing authentic Hakata-style rich, thick and creamy tonkotsu ramen to California. slurpin’ derives from Japanese culture in showing respect to your ramen chef with a loud “slurp” sound from eating the noodles and broth. Loud slurping may seem different in the US, but in Japan it is considered rude not to slurp!
        Grab a bowl and let us hear you enjoy the great quality taste in every slurp!</string>
    <string name="restaurant_slurpin_ramen_bar_hours">Open everyday 11:30am - 12am</string>
    <string name="restaurant_slurpin_ramen_bar_location">18508-A E Gale Ave city of Industry, CA 92748</string>

    <string name="restaurant_native_fields">Native Fields</string>
    <string name="restaurant_native_fields_subtitle">With 100% locally sourced ingredients, we shop at the South Pasadena and Claremont farmers markets. We support local farmers</string>
    <string name="restaurant_native_fields_details">With 100% locally sourced ingredients, we shop at the South Pasadena and Claremont farmers markets. We support local farmers, like Underwood Family Farms, Valdivia Farm, Justin of Seeds of Xanxadu, and Cal Poly Pomona. Native Fields is a farm-to-table, non-GMO, pesticide-free restaurant and cafe. Grass-fed beef, free-range chicken and pasture-raised eggs are served here with vegetarian and vegan options available.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_native_fields_hours">Open Sun - Tue 9am - 3pm, Wen - Sat 9am - 9pm</string>
    <string name="restaurant_native_fields_location">18750 Amar Rd, Walnut, CA 91789</string>

    <string name="restaurant_the_chessecake_factory">The Chessecake Factory</string>
    <string name="restaurant_the_cheesecake_factory_subtitle">With more than 250 items on our menu, it may be hard to believe</string>
    <string name="restaurant_the_cheesecake_factory_details">With more than 250 items on our menu, it may be hard to believe that we make things fresh and from scratch in each restaurant – but it’s true! Our prep kitchens are one of the busiest spots in our restaurants, and it’s where the magic begins every day.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_the_cheesecake_factory_hours">Open M-th 11:30am - 10pm, Fri 11:30am - 11pm, Sat 11am - 11pm, Sun 10am - 10pm</string>
    <string name="restaurant_the_cheesecake_factory_location">189 The Grove Dr K-90, Los Angeles, CA 90036</string>

    <string name="restaurant_viva_madrid">Viva Madrid</string>
    <string name="restaurant_viva_madrid_subtitle">Located in Claremont historic Village district, Viva Madrid has been serving authentic Spanish.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_viva_madrid_details">Located in Claremont historic Village district, Viva Madrid has been serving authentic Spanish flavors and experiences since </string>
    <string name="restaurant_viva_madrid_hours">Open M-Th 5pm - 10pm, Fri 5pm - 11pm, Sat 4pm - 11pm, Sun 4pm - 9pm</string>
    <string name="restaurant_viva_madrid_location">225 N Yale Ave, Claremont, CA 91711</string>

    <string name="restaurant_little_sister">Little Sister DTLA</string>
    <string name="restaurant_little_sister_subtitle">East-Meets-West dishes that inspire and evoke a feeling of being welcomed into Chef</string>
    <string name="restaurant_little_sister_details">"East-Meets-West dishes that inspire and evoke a feeling of being welcomed into Chef Vuong's home. Little Sister's menu showcases Chef Tin's take on one of the more interesting and rich collisions of food and culture that was borne out of the European colonization of Southeast Asia.
        Dishes blend and balance the spices and flavors of Southeast Asia with French techniques and Dutch and British colonial influences. The menu is continually and progressively evolving, reflecting the inspiration and the seasons. Chef Tin curates the restaurant's wine and beverage program with a focus on intriguing labels, both domestically and from around the world."</string>
    <string name="restaurant_little_sister_hours">Open M-F 11am - 10pm, S-Sun 11am - 10pm</string>
    <string name="restaurant_little_sister_location">523 W 7th St, Los Angeles, CA 90017</string>

    <string name="restaurant_mama_por_dios">Mama Por Dios</string>
    <string name="restaurant_mama_por_dios_subtitle">Mamá por Dios is a restaurant that highlights the best of México, with its flavors</string>
    <string name="restaurant_mama_por_dios_details">Mamá por Dios is a restaurant that highlights the best of México, with its flavors, aromas, colors, traditions and art. Bringing it closer to its customers and every drink in every corner. Mamá por Dios is a Mexican gourmet restaurant where you can celebrate every moment to the sound of live Mariachi or enjoy a shot to the beats of a great DJ.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_mama_por_dios_hours">Open Brunch M-Thu 10am - 2pm, Dinner 5pm - 12pm, Fri 11am - 2pm, Sat 10am - 2pm, Sun 10am - 12am</string>
    <string name="restaurant_mama_por_dios_location">12225 E. Foothill Blvd. Rancho Cucamonga, CA. 91739</string>
    <!-- Pet Friendly Restaurants -->
    <string name="pet_friendly_pedalers_fork">Pedalers Fork</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_pedalers_fork_subtitle">Even though Pedalers Fork has deep roots in Los Angeles’s bike culture, it’s also an ideal spot to bring pups. </string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_pedalers_fork_details">Even though Pedalers Fork has deep roots in Los Angeles’s bike culture, it’s also an ideal spot to bring pups. The Calabasas space can provide options if there for a quick coffee stop, or with a full sit-down meal including brisket, maple chili chicken wings, and a hot chicken sandwich.</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_pedalers_fork_hours">Coffee Shop 6am - 3pm, Lunch M - 8am - 1pm, Tue - Fri 8am - 3pm, Weekend Brunch 8am- 2:30pm</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_pedalers_fork_location">23504 Calabasas Rd, Calabasas, CA 91302</string>

    <string name="pet_friendly_tallulas">"Tallula's"</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_tallulas_subtitle">Tallula’s in Santa Monica was always one of Los Angeles’s more dog-friendly spaces</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_tallulas_details">Tallula’s in Santa Monica was always one of Los Angeles’s more dog-friendly spaces (maybe even friendlier than most, with employees consistently coming over to give dog-friends ample treats and love). But with the addition of its new-ish Sunday dog brunch, now a full-time dog menu offered seven days a week, it’s reached a new tier. Dogs can feast on watermelon bites, chicken tacos, and the “wolf’s feast,” a bowl of raw grass-fed hanger steak with steamed vegetables.</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_tallulas_hours">CLOSED</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_tallulas_location">118 Entrada Dr. Santa Monica, CA 90402</string>

    <string name="pet_friendly_sugar_palm_ocean_avenue">Sugar Palm Ocean Avenue</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_sugar_palm_ocean_avenue_subtitle">The Viceroy in Santa Monica is as pet-friendly as it comes, and recently launched</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_sugar_palm_ocean_avenue_detail">The Viceroy in Santa Monica is as pet-friendly as it comes, and recently launched an actual pet menu on Saturdays and Sundays from 6:30 a.m. to 2:30 p.m. That includes a puppy scramble with eggs, spinach, and shredded chicken, or the Snoop Doggy Dog with CBD oil, almond milk, peanut butter, and banana.</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_sugar_palm_ocean_avenue_hours">Brunch 6:30am - 3:00pm, Dinner 3:00pm - 10:0pm</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_sugar_palm_ocean_avenue_location">1819 Ocean Avenue, Santa Monica, California 90401</string>

    <string name="pet_friendly_hermanito">Hermanito</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_hermanito_subtitle">Sawtelle’s best dog-friendly spot is Hermanito: The owner converted the side</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_hermanito_detail">Sawtelle’s best dog-friendly spot is Hermanito: The owner converted the side driveway and rear parking lot into new dining areas (including doggy doors for the “perros”), and it’s something to behold. The tables keep ample space between them, leaving plenty of room to bring dogs while eating the five-spice duck with a cocktail.</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_hermanito_hours">M--Th 11:30am--10:45pm, Fri 11:30--11:45pm, Sat 11:00am--11:45pm, Sun 11:00am--9:00pm</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_hermanito_location">2024 Sawtelle Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90025</string>

    <string name="pet_friendly_highly_likely_cafe">Highly Likely Cafe</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_highly_likely_cafe_subtitle">This all-day cafe in West Adams is the platonic ideal for unrushed, unequivocally easy weekday</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_highly_likely_cafe_detail">This all-day cafe in West Adams is the platonic ideal for unrushed, unequivocally easy weekday and weekend breakfasts. Dogs will appreciate the love and attention from staff members, who are highly likely to pet them or pass on treats as they walk by to drop off squishy-roll bodega breakfast sandwiches and flaky chocolate croissants.</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_highly_likely_cafe_hours">Hours 8am - 9pm Daily</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_highly_likely_cafe_location">4310 W Jefferson Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90016</string>

    <string name="pet_friendly_momed">Momed</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_momed_subtitle">Momed boasts its very own mascot, Piper, who is often roaming</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_momed_detail">Momed boasts its very own mascot, Piper, who is often roaming the grounds of this Middle Eastern hot spot in Atwater Village. Bring friends to keep her company on the spacious shaded patio, and enjoy some of mezze, cocktails, and kabobs to boot.</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_momed_hours">Lunch - Tuesday to Friday 11:30am to 2:30pm, Brunch - Saturday and Sunday 10am to 3pm, Dinner - Sunday to Thursday 5pm to 9:30pm, Dinner - Friday and Saturday 5pm to 10pm, Happy Hour - Monday to Thursday 5pm to 6:30pm</string>
    <string name="pet_friendly_momed_location">3425 Casitas Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90039</string>

    <!--Dog Parks Recommendation -->
    <string name="dog_parks_the_boneyard">The Boneyard</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_the_boneyard_subtitle">The Boneyard is open each day from sunrise until 10:00 pm. This off-leash dog park is located within</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_the_boneyard_detail">The Boneyard is open each day from sunrise until 10:00 pm. This off-leash dog park is located within a large park and features a small and large dog park area, benches, trees, and water fountains in just over a little more than an acre. Decomposed granite is used as ground cover. And don’t forget, dogs must be licensed, vaccinated, and over the age of four months.</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_the_boneyard_hours">Sunrise until 10:00pm</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_the_boneyard_location">Duquesne Ave. and Jefferson Blvd., Culver City, CA 90232</string>

    <string name="dog_parks_arts_district_dog_park">Arts District Dog Park</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_arts_district_dog_park_subtitle">The Arts District Dog Park is a small-ish, private, non-profit dog park and has longer hours than most other dog parks</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_arts_district_dog_park_detail">The Arts District Dog Park is a small-ish, private, non-profit dog park and has longer hours than most other dog parks. It is open daily from 5:00 am to 11:00 pm. Additionally, you’ll find a dog water fountain, a separate area for small dogs, shade trees, and benches. The ground cover is made up of a decomposed granite surface. Visiting dogs must be at least four months old and up-to-date with licenses and vaccines.</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_arts_district_dog_park_hours">Daily 5:00am to 11:00pm</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_arts_district_dog_park_location">1004 E. 4th St., Los Angeles, CA 90013</string>

    <string name="dog_parks_bluff_creek_dog_park">Bluff Creek Dog Park</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_bluff_creek_dog_park_subtitle">You’ll find Bluff Creek Dog Park in the Playa Vista neighborhood of Los Angeles.</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_bluff_creek_dog_park_detail">You’ll find Bluff Creek Dog Park in the Playa Vista neighborhood of Los Angeles. The park is open seven days a week (opening at 7:00 am Monday through Friday, 8:00 am on Saturday and Sunday, and closing at dusk). Bluff Creek is the only dog park in Playa Vista that offers “pet turf” in contrast to the wood chips you’ll find at other parks. You’ll also find “rolling hills” and a central stream</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_bluff_creek_dog_park_hours">Mon- Fri 7:00am to dusk, Sat- Sun 8:00am to dusk</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_bluff_creek_dog_park_location">12604 Bluff Creek Dr., Los Angeles, CA 90094</string>

    <string name="dog_parks_griffith_park_dog_park">Griffith Park Dog Park</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_griffith_park_dog_park_subtitle">The Griffith Park Dog Park is open daily from sunrise to sunset, although it does close each Tuesday from 6:00 am to 10:00 am for maintenance.</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_griffith_park_dog_park_detail">The Griffith Park Dog Park is open daily from sunrise to sunset, although it does close each Tuesday from 6:00 am to 10:00 am for maintenance. This 1.6-acre dog park tends to be most popular with families “in the know” and so doesn’t tend to get as crowded as other parks. You’ll find separate fenced-off areas for small and large dogs, shaded sitting areas, and picnic tables. No grass here, which can make clean-up easier. A visit to Griffith Park Dog Park can also be included into a whole day spent in Griffith Park and its many family-friendly attractions!</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_griffith_park_dog_park_hours">Daily from sunrise to sunset</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_griffith_park_dog_park_location">North end of the John Ferraro Soccer Field on N. Zoo Dr., Los Angeles, CA 90027</string>

    <string name="dog_parks_sepulveda_basin_off_leash_dog_park">Sepulveda Basin Off leash Dog Park</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_sepulveda_basin_off_leash_dog_park_subtitle">The Dog Park is open daily from sunrise to sunset, though it is closed each Fridayn</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_sepulveda_basin_off_leash_dog_park_detail">The Dog Park is open daily from sunrise to sunset, though it is closed each Friday from 6:00 am to 11:00 am for regular maintenance. Families will enjoy this 6.5-acre dog park which offers two small dog runs and one large dog run. You’ll also find lots of trees providing shade as well as benches and chairs. The site also hosts a low-cost Vaccine Clinic each Sunday from 3:30 pm to 5:00 pm.</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_sepulveda_basin_off_leash_dog_park_hours">Daily from sunrise to sunset</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_sepulveda_basin_off_leash_dog_park_location">17550 Victory Blvd., Encino, CA 91406</string>

    <string name="dog_parks_lake_hollywood_park">Lake Hollywood Park</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_lake_hollywood_park_subtitle">The Lake Hollywood Park boasts a children’s play area, picnic tables, barbecue pits</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_lake_hollywood_park_detail">The Lake Hollywood Park boasts a children’s play area, picnic tables, barbecue pits, and an incredible view of the Hollywood sign. In addition, the park is dog-friendly though dogs must remain on leashes. The park is open seven days a week from sunrise to sunset. (Keep in mind the area can get crowded due to visitors trying to catch a glimpse of the Hollywood sign).
</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_lake_hollywood_park_hours">Daily from sunrise to sunset</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_lake_hollywood_park_location">3160 Canyon Lake Dr., Los Angeles, CA</string>

    <string name="dog_parks_silver_lake_dog_park">Silver Lake Dog Park</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_silver_lake_dog_park_subtitle">The Silver Lake Dog Park is open seven days a week, from 6:00 am to 10:00 pm.</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_silver_lake_dog_park_detail">The Silver Lake Dog Park is open seven days a week, from 6:00 am to 10:00 pm. (Note that the park closes each Wednesday from 6:00 am to 8:30 am for regular maintenance). Dogs will enjoy running off-leash at this fenced-in park which has a separate area for smaller pets. Regularly visiting families speak highly of the friendly dogs and dog owners you’ll encounter here, the biggest complaint is the lack of grass.</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_silver_lake_dog_park_hours">Daily from 6:00am to 10:00pm</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_silver_lake_dog_park_location">1863 Silve Lake Blvd., Los Angeles, CA 90026</string>

    <string name="dog_parks_runyon_canyon_dog_park">Runyon Canyon Dog Park</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_runyon_canyon_dog_park_subtitle">Families who enjoy hiking Runyon Canyon will appreciate the convenience of the Runyon</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_runyon_canyon_dog_park_detail">Families who enjoy hiking Runyon Canyon will appreciate the convenience of the Runyon Canyon Dog Park. The dog park is open daily from sunrise to sunset. Families will find beautiful walking trails providing scenic views of our city. There are separate fenced-off areas for small and large dogs. Keep in mind that this is a popular spot, and as is common in Los Angeles, parking can be a challenge sometimes.</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_runyon_canyon_dog_park_hours">Daily from sunrise to sunset</string>
    <string name="dog_parks_runyon_canyon_dog_park_location">2000 N. Fuller Ave., Los Angeles, CA 90046</string>

    <!--Shopping Center Recommendation -->
    <string name="shopping_center_victoria_gardens">Victoria Gardens</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_victoria_gardens_subtitle">The Victoria Gardens Cultural Center, which features the Rancho Cucamonga</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_victoria_gardens_detail">The Victoria Gardens Cultural Center, which features the Rancho Cucamonga Public Library, a performing arts center, and a multi-use reception hall, is owned and operated by the city of Rancho Cucamonga and sits north of the shopping center between the two parking structures</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_victoria_gardens_hours">Mon- Thu 10:00am to 8:00pm, Fri- Sat 10:00am to 9:00pm and Sun 11:00am to 7:00pm</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_victoria_gardens_location">12505 North Mainstreet Rancho Cucamonga, CA 91739</string>

    <string name="shopping_center_ontario_mills">Ontario Mills</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_ontario_mills_subtitle">Ontario Mills is a shopping and outlet mall located in Ontario, California</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_ontario_mills_detail">Ontario Mills is a shopping and outlet mall located in Ontario, California, within the Los Angeles metropolitan area. With 28 million annual visitors, it is one of the top shopping and tourist destinations in California.</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_ontario_mills_hours">10:00am to 9:00pm</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_ontario_mills_location">1 Mills Cir, Ontario, CA 91764</string>

    <string name="shopping_center_the_grove">The Grove</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_the_grove_subtitle">High-end shopping mall features trendy retailers</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_the_grove_detail">High-end shopping mall features trendy retailers, restaurants and a theater amid a bustling promenade.</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_the_grove_hours">10:00am to 10:00pm</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_the_grove_location">189 The Groove Dr, Los Angeles, CA 90036</string>

    <string name="shopping_center_south_coast_plaza">South Coast Plaza</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_south_coast_plaza_subtitle">South Coast Plaza is a modern shopping hub in the heart of Orange County, attracting those seeking upscale boutiques,</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_south_coast_plaza_detail">South Coast Plaza is a modern shopping hub in the heart of Orange County, attracting those seeking upscale boutiques, designer labels, and award-winning cuisine. With one of the greatest concentrations of high-fashion retailers, rivaling the trendsetting neighborhoods of Bond Street, London and Fifth Avenue, New York, you are bound to leave with a celebrity-worthy wardrobe.
With a cascading multitier fountain as its centerpiece, the 3-floor shopping mall is designed in a wonky H-shape, with 2 parking neighborhoods and a V.I.P. concierge service. Department stores are positioned around the perimeter, while boutique shops are grouped by product. High-end jewelers call Jewel Court home, while Carousel Court is where you go for hip, big-name apparel options.</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_south_coast_plaza_hours"> Mon- Fri from 10:00am to 9:00pm Sat 10:00am to 8:00pm, Sun 11:00am to 6:30pm</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_south_coast_plaza_location">3333 Bristol Street, Costa Mesa, CA 92626</string>

    <string name="shopping_center_hollywood_and_highland">Hollywood and Highland</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_hollywood_and_highland_subtitle">There is never a dull moment on Hollywood Boulevard and the same goes for the shopping at Hollywood and Highland</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_hollywood_and_highland_detail">There is never a dull moment on Hollywood Boulevard and the same goes for the shopping at Hollywood and Highland. Boasting iconic tourist attractions such as the TCL Chinese Theatre, the Dolby Theatre and the Walk of Fame, this mall offers just as much gravy in its range of shops.
Familiar favorites include Gap, American Eagle and LA’s only Virgin Megastore, as well as smaller chains like Swatch, Bebe and Hot Topic. If you’re looking to take something back home, the mall also has excellent souvenir shops. Though Hollywood and Highland may be crowded, its easily understandable thanks to its legendary status.</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_hollywood_and_highland_hours">Mon- Sat 10:00am to 10:00pm, Sun from 10:00am to 8:00pm</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_hollywood_and_highland_location">6801 Hollywood Boulevard 170, Los Angeles, CA 90028</string>

    <string name="shopping_center_santa_monica_place">Santa Monica Place</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_santa_monica_place_subtitle">With Santa Monica Place just blocks from the beach, a dip in the ocean and a trip to the shops became just as easy</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_santa_monica_place_detail">With Santa Monica Place just blocks from the beach, a dip in the ocean and a trip to the shops became just as easy. Worth mentioning is its sleek, modern open-air design which involves a rooftop dining deck with chef-driven restaurants and stunning views of the city, the mountains and the Pacific.
The mall has shops that range from Louis Vuitton Ted Baker to Bloomingdale’s and Nordstrom. But the experience is made all the more special with the mall’s superb dining options and a state-of-the-art 12-screen movie theater experience… you could spend a few days here</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_santa_monica_place_hours">Mon- Sat from 10:00am to 9:00pm, Sun from 11:00am to 8:00pm</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_santa_monica_place_location">395 Santa Monica Place, Santa Monica, CA 90401</string>


    <string name="location_text">Location: </string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
</resources>